What exactly did you do on your day-to-day in
your position at HMS and what was the most
impactful part of that position? So let me drop back
a little bit and give you a bit of my journey.
I started at HMS and I was
the head of commercial sales and account management.
Then after a year, the head of federal and
state decided to leave the company and so the CEO
said, Doug, you go take over state and
federal. So now I had commercial, state, federal, sales,
account management, marketing, and government relations.
So I ran everything at HMS that
touched a customer. We're about $400 million at the
time, roughly as a run rate. The next four
years, I really worked in that role and then
one of our divisions was having a huge challenge and
I asked the CEO if he would put me in
charge of that. Brought in someone else to run all the
client-facing stuff and I ultimately ended up
taking over our COB business, our payment integrity
business, and our IT shop. So
I moved from a fully externally facing
individual to a fully external-facing individual. So
I moved from a fully externally facing individual
to basically running the operations of the company.